<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NetflixcloneApp</string>
    <string name="simple_text"> honestly think it’s so dumb when people are “waiting for their real life to begin.
        ” Like honey, it’s all real! What do you think the past 20 or so years of your life have been? Just go out and do the things you want to do and stop waiting for some defining moment that symbolizes the beginning of your “real” life. Whatever that means. (Why did I just get so deep?) (Also, this movie looks fun and I intend to watch it.)</string>
    <string name="simple_cast"> Since 2002, there have been three Spider-Men in the Marvel Cinematic Universe, each with a slightly different approach to the character. All were awkward (at least when they weren’t swinging between buildings as superheroes), and each had a heavy interest in science. But we think it’s safe to say that the first two webslingers (Tobey Maguire and Andrew Garfield) were more angst-ridden and dealt with more heavy emotional issues. They were both also fairly obvious Introverts – at least until they donned the mask and took on a new persona.

Spider-Man Personality
The third and most recent movie version of Spider-Man (Tom Holland) just seems to want to be liked and to do good things. The sad demise of Uncle Ben isn’t even much of an issue in his story line and is part of an origin story that happens before we meet this incarnation. (Thankfully. We’ve already seen it twice with the previous two Spider-Men.) Overall, Holland’s Spider-Man is a much more carefree character.

Peter Parker, watching the girl he likes: We better stop staring before it turns creepy.

Michelle: Too late.

When not fighting crime, Holland’s Peter Parker deals with a lot of worries that may be familiar to high school aged individuals. His love life so far seems to be limited to a heavy crush rather than a real romance. When fighting crime, he does so with youthful exuberance. He’s far more different from the previous two Spider-Men than Tobey Maguire’s and Andrew Garfield’s interpretations of the character were from each other. For this article, the focus will be on the Tom Holland version of Peter Parker.

This Peter Parker’s Personality Type
So, let’s call it. The latest incarnation of PeterParker is, we believe, a Turbulent Campaigner (ENFP-T). Here’s how we figure it.

Extraverted
Holland’s Peter Parker wants nothing more than to jump into the fray – a prominent feature of Extraversion. His social life is weak, but it’s not because he doesn’t want one. He may not be a social A-lister in high school, but it’s not because he prefers to be alone. It’s just that as a dedicated crime fighter, he has little time to cultivate many friendships outside of class.

Peter’s eager to be accepted as a member of the Avengers, although he remains on the periphery. His banter is nonstop – not just while hiding behind a mask, like other versions of the character, but even as Peter Parker (see his back-and-forth with bodega owner Mr. Delmar in Homecoming.) He’s not only outgoing with people, but he’s also eager to enjoy all the experiences his unique powers offer him.

Intuitive
Watching Peter act, one gets the sense that he is responding to general impressions rather than specific evidence – a key element of the Intuitive personality trait. He’s more attuned to the overarching ideal of being a hero than the nitty-gritty of solving problems in a concrete way.

Peter believes that as long as he is trying in good faith, that should be enough for Tony Stark to bless his endeavors, regardless of his level of effectiveness. His Intuition, paired with his Feeling trait, makes him an idealistic personality who sees himself as a cog in a machine that will bring about a better, safer world.


</string>
</resources>